爸爸走了
Dad's gone now.
他希望我们继续他的事业
He wants us to pick up where he left off.
怎么样 我们一起去杀些凶鬼恶灵
What do you say we kill some evil sons of bitches.
惹点麻烦吧
And we raise a little hell?
（忆往昔）
她真名叫贝拉·塔伯特
Bela Talbot's her real name.
她是猎人吗
Is she a hunter?
才不是呢
Pretty frigging far from a hunter.
我为特定客户获取一些独特的东西
I procure unique items for a select clientele.
贼
A thief.
是神偷
A great thief.
我想你会发现那是我的
I think you'll find that belongs to me.
你不会开枪的
You're not gonna shoot anybody.
你遇见过一个叫戈登·沃克的人吗
You ever run across a guy named Gordon Walker?
我知道了
I know…
关于萨姆能看到幻象
I know about Sam's visions.
我什么都知道了
I know everything.
戈登接下来几年里
Gordon should be reaching for the soap.
肯定要捡肥皂了
for the next few years at least.
你全都说对了
You were right about everything.
萨姆·温彻斯特不是单纯的怪物
Sam Winchester is more than a monster.
我都不确定他是人类
I'm not even sure he's human.
我们得想办法帮我越狱
We gotta get me the hell out of here.
（如今）
偷偷靠近别人可不礼貌
It's rude to sneak up on people.
贝拉·塔伯特
Bela Talbot.
我处于劣势了
You have me at a disadvantage.
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are.
戈登·沃克
Gordon Walker.
我听说过你
I've heard of you.
听说你在监狱里呢
Heard you were in prison.
出来了
Got out.
表现良好提前释放吗
Released early on good behavior?
找这个吗
Looking for this?
我知道你才去过马萨诸塞州
I know you were just in Massachusetts.
我还知道温家兄弟当时也跟你在一起
And I know you were with the Winchester boys.
告诉我们他们在哪
Tell me where they are.
我恐怕不知道
I don't think I know.
再好好想想吧
Why don't you think a little harder?
放下那个
Put that down.
为什么这么急着找到他们
What's so pressing about finding the boys, anyway?
萨姆·温彻斯特是反基督
Sam Winchester is the Antichrist.
- 这我有所耳闻 - 是真的
- I'd heard something about that. - It's true.
是我的好朋友 复活节兔子告诉我的
From my good friend, the Easter bunny.
它是听牙仙说的
Who'd heard it from the tooth fairy.
你是没吃药吗
Are you off your meds?
事关世界安危
The world hangs in the balance.
你尽管自作聪明吧
So you go ahead and be a smart-ass.
告诉我他们在哪
Tell me where they are.
否则我就开枪了
or I shoot.
戈登 你和我不怎么熟悉
Gordon, you and I don't know each other very well.
所以让我跟你讲讲我吧
So let me tell you a little something about me.
我不理睬威胁
I don't respond well to threats.
但如果你给我开个价
But you make me an offer,
我就会很乐意配合
and I think you'll find me highly cooperative.
好
Okay.
这样吧 你告诉我他们在哪
How about, you tell me where they are.
否则我这就杀了你
or I kill you right now.
杀了我吧
Kill me.
祝你能找到萨姆和迪恩
Good luck finding Sam and Dean.
我可以凑到三千
I can wrangle up three grand.
我才不会为了三千起床
I don't get out of bed for three grand.
忘了那个吧
Scratch that.
把魔力袋给我 我们就算两清了
Give me the mojo bag and we'll call it even.
别想
Hell, no.
这玩意有一个世纪的历史
This thing's a century old,
- 是… - 无价之宝
- it's… - Priceless.
相信我 我知道
Believe me, I know.
你有多想找到温家兄弟
Now, how badly do you want the Winchesters?
你好 迪恩
Hello, Dean.
你在哪呢
Where are you?
[邪恶力量 第3季第7集]
别担心
Don't worry, don't worry.
我们会帮你求助的
We're gonna call you some help, okay?
她在哪
Where is she?
她去哪了
Where'd she go?
闻到了吗
Smell that?
来吸啊
Come and get it!
没错 来吧
That's right. Come on.
我闻起来很不错吧
I smell good, don't I?
我尝起来更棒
I taste even better.
来啊
Come on.
免费午餐
Free lunch.
怎么了
What?
刚刚有点悬吧
Cutting it a little close, don't you think?
只是下饵罢了
I was just chumming the water.
不是成功了吗
Worked, didn't it?
你醒了
You with us?
嗯 抱歉
Yeah. Sorry,
你哪都别想去
you're not going anywhere.
- 什么… - 你的血巢在哪
- Wha…? - Where's your nest?
- 什么 - 你的血巢
- What? - Your nest.
你和你的吸血伙伴住在哪
Where you and your bloodsucking pals hang out?
我不知道你们在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
拜托 我感觉不好
Please, I don't feel good.
是啊
Yeah, well.
如果我们再给你注射死人血
You're gonna feel hell of a lot worse,
你的感觉只会更糟
if we give you another shot of Dead Man's Blood.
放了我吧
Just let me go.
你知道我们不能那么做
Yeah, you know we can't do that.
我说的是实话
I'm telling you the truth.
我…
I'm just…
我服了某种东西
I took something.
我好抓狂 我不知道这是怎么回事
I'm freaking out, I don't know what's going on.
- 你服了某种东西 - 对
- You took something? - Yes.
药效怎么都不过去
I can't come down.
我只想让它过去
I just wanna come down.
你叫什么
What's your name?
露西
Lucy.
拜托 放了我吧
Please, just let me go.
好吧 露西 这样吧
All right, Lucy, how about this?
你告诉我们发生了什么
If you tell us what happened…
我们就放了你
we'll let you go.
真的吗
You will?
我不…
I don't really…
我记得不太清楚了
It's… It's not that clear.
- 我当时在蜘蛛 - 蜘蛛
- I was at Spider. - Spider?
杰斐逊街的一家夜店
The club, on Jefferson.
有个男人 他请我喝酒
And there was this guy, he was buying me drinks.
这人
This guy.
他什么样
What's he look like?
挺旧的 30岁吧
He was old, like, 30.
他棕色头发 穿皮夹克
He had brown hair, a leather jacket.
叫迪康还是迪克森的
Deacon or Dixon or something.
他说他是毒贩 可以给我点药
Said he was a dealer, he had something for me.
- 药 - 新药
- Something? - Something new.
前所未有的好药
Better than anything you ever tried.
他往我的酒里滴了几滴
He put a few drops in my drink.
那药是红色粘稠质地的吗
Was the drug red and thick?
真是天才之举
Well, genius move there.
- 他给你下的是吸血鬼血 - 什么
- That was vampire blood he dosed you with. - What?
对 你喝下了这世上
Yeah. You just took a big steaming shot.
最可怕的病毒
of the nastiest virus out there.
你疯了吧 他是给我下了迷奸药之类的
You're crazy, he gave me roofies or something.
不
No.
接下来 我们就去了他家
The next thing I know, we're at his place…
他说他会去给我找东西吃 让我等着
and he says he's gonna get me something to eat, just wait.
但我好饿
But I get so hungry.
所以你就冲了出去
So you busted out?
对
Yeah.
但药效怎么都不过去
But it won't wear off…
他给我的那不知什么药
whatever he gave me.
光线太亮吗
Lights too bright?
阳光伤你的皮肤吗
Sunshine hurts your skin?
对
Yeah.
还有气味
And smells.
我还能听到血液涌动
And I can hear blood pumping.
我也不想说这个 亲爱的
Well, I hate to tell you this, sweetheart,
但你的血再不会涌动了
but your blood's never pumping again.
不是我
Not mine.
是你的血
Yours.
我能在半个街区外听到心跳声
I can hear a heart beating from half a block away.
我只想让它停下来
I just want it to stop.
好吧 听着 嬉皮姑娘
All right, listen, Wavy Gravy.
这感觉不会停了
It's not going to stop.
你已经杀了两个人 差点杀了第三个
You've already killed two people, almost three.
不 不可能
No, I couldn't.
不 那是幻觉
No, I was hallucinating.
你杀了他们
You killed them.
我们一直在追踪一堆处理大意的尸体
All right. We've been following a sloppy trail of corpses.
- 直接带我们找到了你 - 不
- And it leads straight to you. - No.
不 那不是真的
No, it wasn't real.
是那药的效果
It was the drug.
拜托
Please.
拜托 你们得帮帮我
Please, you have to help me.
不
No, no.
可怜的姑娘
Poor girl.
我们没别的办法
We don't have a choice.
不要
No.
求你
Please.
先生
Sir.
问几个关于袭击的问题
A few questions about the attack.
我已经跟警察谈过了
I already talked to the cops.
我们不是警察
Well, we're not cops.
我们是联调局
We're FBI.
联调局
FBI?
可以形容下袭击者吗
Can you describe your attacker?
她是个疯子
She was crazy.
她有服了迷幻剂后的超大力气
She had that, uh, super PCP strength, you know?
她咬了我的脖子
She gnawed on my neck.
她把血滴在你身上了吗
And did she bleed on you?
在我身上 没有
On me? No.
滴在你嘴里 或切开的伤口里 有吗
In your mouth, open wound, anything?
你确定吗
You sure about that?
嗯 我确定 你为什么问这个
Yeah, I'm sure. Why do you ask?
这女人携带了非常危险的病毒
This woman has a very dangerous virus.
什么
What?
她咬了我的脖子
S-She bit me in the neck.
咬伤不要紧
The bite doesn't matter.
你要摄入她的血才会被感染
You have to actually ingest the blood to be infected.
幸好啊
Good thing too.
否则我们只能杀了你
We'd have had to kill you.
- 袭击呢 - 她扑倒了我 然后咬了我
- The attack? - She jumped me, then bit me.
然后那俩男人发现了我
And then those two guys found me, and,
追着她进了小巷
chased her down the alley.
他们什么样
What did they look like?
我没看得很清楚
I didn't get a good look.
好好想想
Think.
其中一个很高
One of them was real tall.
（蜘蛛）
真是浪费时间
That was a big fat waste of time.
听着
Look.
已有三个金发女孩失踪 包括露西
Three blonds have gone missing, including Lucy.
最后被看到都是在这里
All last sighted here.
相信我 迪恩 这是他的狩猎区
I'm telling you, Dean, this is the hunting ground.
你真变态
You're sick.
准备好了吗 亲爱的
You ready, sweetie?
尝一口这个 你就会彻底改变
One taste of this, you'll never be the same.
快走 走
Get out of here. Go, go.
迪恩
Dean.
我没事 来
I'm good. Come on.
好吧
All right,
你跑 我去引开他们
run, I'll draw them off.
什么 不 你疯了
What? No, you're crazy.
你可回来了
There you are.
嗯
Yeah,
抱歉 我半路去吃披萨了
sorry. I stopped for a slice.
你刚刚真行啊 迪恩
Nice move you pulled back there, Dean,
正冲着武器就去了
running right at the weapons.
没办法
Well, what can I say?
我就是屌
I'm a badass.
看来戈登出狱了
So I guess Gordon's out of jail.
是啊 看来是
Yeah, I guess so.
他怎么知道我们在哪的
You know, how the hell did he know where to find us?
那贱人
That bitch.
- 贝拉 - 你好 迪恩
- Bela. - Hello, Dean.
问你个问题
Question for you.
你昨天给我打电话
You called me yesterday.
并不是为了感谢我救你吧
It wasn't to thank me for saving your ass, was it?
不是
No.
戈登·沃克给我报酬让我说出你们在哪
Gordon Walker paid me to tell him where you were.
什么
Excuse me?
他拿枪指着我呢
Well, he had a gun on me.
我还能怎么办
What else was I supposed to do?
我不知道 或许打电话
I don't know, maybe pick up the phone.
告诉我们有个凶巴巴的疯子要来
And tell us that a raging psychopath was dropping by?
我本打算打电话的 就是有事忘了
I did fully intend to call. I just got a bit sidetracked.
他企图杀我们
He tried to kill us!
抱歉 我不知道这事这么重要
I'm sorry. I didn't realize it was such a big deal.
毕竟 你们是两个人 他是一个人
After all, there are two of you and one of him.
他们也是两个人
There were two of them.
贝拉 如果我们能活下来
Bela, if we make it out of this alive…
我第一件要做的事就是杀了你
the first thing I'm gonna do is kill you.
你不是说真的吧
You're not serious.
好好听我的声音 你说我是不是说真的
Listen to my voice, and tell me if I'm serious.
我知道你觉得不舒服
I know you're uncomfortable…
但这只是暂时的
But this is just temporary.
饥饿感会过去 然后你就会觉得好多了
The hunger will pass and then you'll feel much better.
你醒了
You're awake.
她们是谁
Who are they?
家人
Family.
你总铐着你的家人吗
You always keep your family in shackles?
我们还在熟悉彼此
We're still getting to know each other.
她们才刚重生
They've just been reborn.
你是说 你从街上抓走了几个可怜的姑娘
You mean, you grabbed some poor girls off the street,
把她们变成了你这样的怪物
and made them monsters like you?
我做我必须做的
I do what I have to.
我们都要绝种了
We're a dying breed.
但是
But then,
这你很清楚 是吧 戈登
you know that, don't you, Gordon?
戈登·沃克
Gordon Walker.
当世最伟大的吸血鬼猎人之一
One of the greatest living vampire hunters.
正是本人
In the flesh.
你是我族人几乎绝种的重要原因之一 戈登
You're a big part of why my people are nearly extinct, Gordon.
你族人要绝种
Your people are going extinct,
是因为你们是一群无脑嗜血的动物
because you're a bunch of mindless, bloodthirsty animals.
是啊 我们比你嗜血多了
Right, we're so much more bloodthirsty than you.
猎人屠杀了我的整个血巢
Hunters slaughtered my entire nest.
就像是在开派对
like they were having a party.
杀了我女儿
Murdered my daughter.
我都无法形容这种满足感多强烈
I can't tell you how satisfying this is.
抓到杀死那么多人的猎人
Catching a hunter responsible for so many deaths…
让你做我新女儿的午餐
and making you lunch for my new daughters.
女儿吗
Daughters?
尖牙婊吧
Try fang-whores.
说话小心点
Watch your mouth.
我伤到你的感情了吗
Did I hurt your feelings?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我忘了 你只是个被误解的受害者
I forgot, you're just a misunderstood victim.
虽然你杀人
Even though you murder.
还在原始本能的趋势下传播你的疾病
and spread your filthy disease on pure base instinct.
你还不如下水道的老鼠有人性
You got less humanity than a sewer rat.
很遗憾你对我的族人看法这么差
I'm sorry you have such a low opinion of my people.
你无法想象
You have no idea.
抱歉 计划有变
Sorry, change of plans.
我会出去另给你们找午餐
I'll be going out to get you lunch.
我有更好的办法处置你
I've got a better idea for you.
不
No.
No!
那吸血鬼还在外面呢 迪恩
That vampire's still out there, Dean.
先做重要的事
First things first.
戈登
Gordon.
关于那个
About that.
- 等我们找到他 或他找到我们 - 嗯
- When we find him or if he finds us… - Yeah?
我就是说 他没给我们多少选择了
Well, I'm just saying. He's not leaving us whole lot of options.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
我们得杀了他
We gotta kill him.
是吗 这么爽快吗
Really? Just like that?
还以为你会说
I thought you would've been, like:
「那不行 他是人 这是不对的」
"No, we can't, he's a human, it's wrong."
不 我受够了
No, I'm done.
戈登不会罢休的 除非他杀死我们
I mean, Gordon's not gonna stop until we're dead.
或我们杀死他
Or until he is.
- 干吗 - 我不喜欢被人记仇
- What? - I don't like it when people hold grudges against me.
更重要的是 我不希望被你杀掉
And more to the point, I'd rather you didn't kill me.
所以我替你找到了戈登的准确地址
So I went ahead and found Gordon's exact location for you.
你在百英里外呢
You're hundred miles away.
- 你怎么… - 拜托
- How the hell…? - Hello.
强大魔物供应商啊
Purveyor of powerful occult objects.
我用了通灵板联系了另一边
I used a talking board to contact the other side.
- 怎么样 - 仓库
- And? - Warehouse.
两层 河滨 外面有霓虹灯牌
Two stories, riverfront, neon sign outside.
- 谢谢 - 还有件事
- Thanks. - One more thing.
鬼魂有话告诉你
The spirit had a message for you.
「离开 拼命跑 无论如何
"Leave town, run like hell, and whatever you do,
别去找戈登「
don't go after Gordon."
反正告诉你了
For whatever that's worth.
拜托
Please.
救救我们
Help us.
求你
Please.
来吧
Go ahead.
动手吧
Do it.
杀了我吧
Kill me.
这里发生了什么
What happened here?
戈登·沃克
Gordon Walker.
我就不该把猎人带回来
I never should have brought a hunter here.
真不该
Never.
我…
I just…
我就想报仇
I just wanted some kind of revenge.
好蠢啊 让他见到我的家人
So stupid, exposing him to my family.
是啊 你真是个顾家男人
Yeah, you're such a family man.
你们不懂
You don't understand.
我才不想懂你个混…
I don't wanna understand, you son…
我走投无路了
I was desperate.
你有过那种感觉吗
Have you ever felt desperate?
我失去了我爱的每个人
I've lost everyone I ever loved.
我要孤独地面对永恒
I'm staring down eternity, alone.
你能想到更可怕的地狱吗
Can you think of a worse hell?
还有地狱嘛
Well, there's hell.
我没多想
I wasn't thinking.
我…
I just…
我不在乎了
I didn't care anymore.
你知道那是什么感觉吗
Do you know what that's like?
不在乎
When you just don't give a damn?
就像…
It's like…
就像心死
It's like being dead already.
来吧
So just go ahead.
动手吧
Do it.
迪恩
Dean.
头不是砍掉的 是扯掉的
Head wasn't cut off, it was ripped off.
有人赤手扯掉的
By someone's bare hands.
迪克森
Dixon?
你对戈登做了什么
What did you do to Gordon?
戈登
Gordon.
你还好吗
You okay?
非常不好
Not even close.
我以为你死了呢
I thought maybe you were dead.
怎么了
What is it?
发生了件事
Something happened.
怎么了
What?
他们转化了我
They turned me.
他们 尖牙吗
They? Those fangs?
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
你清楚这意味着什么
You know what this means?
这意味着你必须杀了我
It means you have to kill me.
但先别
But not yet.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你得让我先做完最后一件事
You have to let me do one last thing first.
- 什么 - 杀了萨姆·温彻斯特
- What? - Kill Sam Winchester.
- 戈登 - 这是唯一…
- Gordon… - It's the only…
这是这桩噩梦唯一的好处
It is the one good thing to come out of this nightmare.
我变强壮 敏捷了 我能干掉他
I'm stronger, I'm faster. I can finish him.
戈登
Gordon…
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你知道我不能放你走
You know I can't let you walk out of here.
听我说 这世上没有比这更重要的事了
Listen to me. There is nothing more important.
求你
Please.
我可以为这世界做最后一件好事
I can do one last good thing for the world.
嗯
Yeah.
我明白
I hear you.
戈登
You know, Gordon…
你说得对
you're right.
最后一件好事
One last good thing.
对不起
I'm sorry.
天啊 我都查了三十几家旅馆
Man, I must have checked three dozen motels,
空楼 仓库了
empty buildings, warehouses.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
- 城市很大 - 简直像茫茫大海
- Big city. - It's like a giant haystack.
戈登就是根致命的针
Gordon's a deadly needle.
要天黑了
We're running out of daylight.
没有了太阳的拖累
Without the sun slowing him down…
- 嗯 他会不可阻挡 - 嗯
- Yeah, he'll be unstoppable. - Yeah.
你手机给我
Give me your phone.
干什么
What for?
如果戈登知道我们的手机号
Well, if Gordon knows our cell numbers…
他能利用手机信号追踪我们
he can use the cell signal to track us down.
嗯
Yeah.
- 好 - 嗯
- Nice. - Yeah.
萨姆 待在这里
Sam, stay here.
干吗 你去哪
What? Where are you going now?
我去找戈登
I'm going after Gordon.
什么
What?
没错 你听到了
Yeah, you heard me.
你别想一个人去
Well, not alone, you're not.
萨姆 我不需要你给我签准假条
Sam, I don't need you to sign me a permission slip, okay?
他在追杀你 不是我 他还变身超人了
He's after you, not me, and he's turbocharged.
我要你远离危险
I want you to stay out of harm's way.
我来解决此事
I'll take care of it.
迪恩 你别想自己去
Well, Dean, you're not going by yourself.
你会害死自己的
You're gonna get yourself killed.
那也只是普通的工作日
Just another day at the office.
非常危险的工作日
It's a massively dangerous day at the office.
怎么 你现在是个不怕死的人了
So what, you're the guy with nothing to lose now?
等等 我猜猜 因为
Wait, let me guess. Because…
你反正也已经死了 是吗
It's because you're already dead. Right?
- 既然事实如此 - 知道吗
- If the shoe fits. - You know what, man,
我受够了你的敢死队作风
I'm sick and tired of your old stupid kamikaze trip.
敢死队
Kamikaze?
我更像个忍者
I'm more like a ninja.
这不好笑
That's not funny.
- 有点好笑 - 才不呢
- It's a little funny. - No, it's not.
你想要我做什么 萨姆
What do you want me to do, Sam?
整天闲坐着 写关于我要死了的悲情诗歌吗
Sit around all day, writing sad poems about how I'm gonna die?
知道吗 我想到了一首
You know what? I've got one.
- 什么跟「闭嘴 萨姆」押韵 - 哥们
- See, what rhymes with "Shut up, Sam"? - Dude,
别这么犯浑了 迪恩
drop the attitude, Dean.
别总把一切当做笑话
Quit turning everything into a punch line.
而且知道吗
And you know something else?
别再假装你不害怕了
Stop trying to act like you're not afraid.
- 我不害怕 - 你撒谎
- I'm not. - You're lying.
你别装了 因为我能看穿你
And you may as well drop it because I can see right through you.
你根本在说胡话
You got no idea what you're talking about.
我没有
Yeah, I do.
你在害怕 迪恩
You're scared, Dean.
你害怕 因为你的一年要结束了
You're scared because your year's running out…
你没有摆脱下地狱的命运 你很慌
and you're still going to hell and you're freaked.
- 你怎么知道 - 因为我了解你
- And how do you know that? - Because I know you.
- 是吗 - 对
- Really? - Yeah.
因为我这辈子一直跟着你转
Because, I've been following you around my entire life.
我从四岁起就一直敬仰你 迪恩
I mean, I've been looking up to you since I was 4, Dean.
有样学样 想长大跟我大哥一样
Studying you, trying to be just like my big brother.
所以 是的 我了解你
So yeah, I know you.
比这世上任何人都了解你
Better than anyone else in the entire world.
这…
And this…
正是你非常害怕时的样子
is exactly how you act when you're terrified.
我不怪你
And, I mean, I can't blame you.
就是…
It's just…
怎么了
What?
我希望你能别再装了 做回我哥哥
It's just I wish you would drop the show and be my brother again.
因为
Because…
不因为什么
Just because.
好吧 我们躲在这里
All right, we'll hole up.
掩盖气息 让他无法追踪我们
Cover our scent so he can't track us.
在这里挨过这一晚
Wait the night out here.
这手机你才买了两小时 迪恩
You've had that phone two hours, Dean.
你把号码给谁了
Who'd you give the number to?
没给任何人
Nobody.
- 喂 - 迪恩
- Hello? - Dean.
你怎么拿到这号码的
How'd you get this number?
手机店里都是你的气味
Scent's all over the cell phone store.
当然了 我现在闻不到你了
Of course, I can't smell you now.
你在哪
Where are you?
你只能找到我们了 是吧
I guess you'll just have to find us, won't you?
我更希望你自己来找我
I'd rather you come to me.
怎么了 戈登
What's the matter, Gord-o?
你不是怕我们吧
You're not afraid of us, are you?
我们就坐在这里 来啊
We're just sitting here. Bring it on.
还是不了
I don't think so.
求你
Please, please.
收费公路边的河滨工厂
Factory on Riverside off the turnpike.
20分钟内到
Be here in 20 minutes…
- 否则姑娘就死 - 戈登 放了她
- or the girl dies. - Gordon, let the girl go.
- 再见 迪恩 - 戈登
- Bye, Dean. - Gordon,
别这么做
don't do this.
你不会杀无辜者 你还是个猎人
You don't kill innocent people, you're still a hunter.
不
No.
我是个怪物
I'm a monster.
我们来了
We got you.
别担心 我们救你出去
Don't worry, we're gonna get you out of here.
好了
Okay. Okay.
有我们呢 来 扶她起来
We got you. Come on. Get her up.
小心脑袋
Watch your head. Watch your head.
好了
Okay, okay.
萨姆 跟紧
Sam, stay close.
- 萨姆 - 迪恩
- Sam! - Dean!
该死 萨姆
Damn it, Sam!
萨姆 小心点
Sam, be careful.
戈登
Gordon.
你如愿困住我了
You got me where you want me.
怎么不出来跟我打
Might as well come out and fight.
我在这里呢 萨姆
I'm right here, Sam.
怎么了 萨姆
What's the matter, Sammy?
你就想这么做吗
So this is really the way you wanna do it?
没错
Damn right I do.
你不知道我经历了什么
You have no idea what I faced…
才走到这一步
to get here.
我失去了一切
I lost everything.
我的生命
My life.
但是值得的
But it's worth it.
因为我终于要杀掉
Because I'm finally gonna kill.
我猎杀过的最危险的东西了
the most dangerous thing I ever hunted.
你不是人 萨姆
You're not human, Sam.
你也好意思说
Look who's talking.
是啊
You're right.
我是个嗜血杀手
I'm a bloodthirsty killer.
别说得好像你没得选
Don't talk about it like you don't have a choice.
我是没有
I don't.
你有 戈登
Yes, you do, Gordon.
你就没杀那女孩
You didn't kill that girl.
我是没有
No, I didn't.
我做了糟糕得多的事
I did something much, much worse.
真得承认 萨姆
I gotta hand it to you, Sam.
你蒙蔽了好多人
You got a lot of people fooled.
但我清楚真相
But see, I know the truth.
我清楚那是什么感觉
I know what it's like.
我们现在一样了 你和我
We're the same now, you and me.
我知道与邪恶共存的感觉了
I know how it is walking around with something evil inside you.
真可惜 你不愿做该做的事 自杀
It's just too bad you won't do the right thing and kill yourself.
我会自杀的
I'm gonna.
等我杀了你之后
Soon as I'm done with you.
最后两件好事
Two last good-deeds:
杀你 自杀
Killing you and killing myself.
不
No!
你刚不带武器冲向了吸血鬼化的戈登
You just charged a super-vamped-out Gordon with no weapon.
有点鲁莽吧
It's a little reckless, don't you think?
给
Here you go.
- 谢谢 - 查出嘎嘎声是什么发出的了吗
- Thanks. - Figure out what's making that rattle?
还没呢
Not yet.
给我个管扳手 好吗
Give me a box wrench, would you?
嗯
Yeah.
给
Here you go.
- 谢谢 - 嗯
- Thanks. - Yeah.
萨姆
Sam.
拿错了吗
Wrong one?
不是 过来一下
No, no, no. Come here for a second.
嗯
Yeah.
那嘎嘎声有几种可能
This rattle could be a couple of things.
我觉得是汽化器问题
I'm thinking it's an out of tune carb.
好吧
Okay.
好 你看这个 这是阀盖
All right, see this thing? It's a valve cover.
里面是各种气缸盖零件
Inside are all the parts that are on the head.
给我那把套筒扳手
Give me that socket wrench.
好 你跟得上吧
All right, you with me so far?
嗯
Yeah,
阀盖盖住气缸盖
valve cover covers the heads.
很好 这是进气歧管
Very good. Now, this is your intake manifold, okay?
上面是
On top of it…
是…
It's a…
汽化器吗
A carburetor?
- 汽化器 - 嗯
- Carburetor. - Yeah.
很好
Very good.
干吗突然教我修车
What's with the auto shop?
怎么 你难道是要…
What? You don't mean you want…?
对 没错
Yeah, I do.
你来修
You fix it.
迪恩 你都不怎么让我开它
Dean, you barely let me drive this thing.
时候到了
No, it's time.
你该会修
You should know how to fix it.
你需要学会这些东西 将来用得上
You're gonna need to know these things for the future.
再说 这是我的职责嘛
And besides, it's my job, right?
教我弟弟做事
Showing my little brother the ropes.
用点力气
Put your shoulder into it.